Attila Kun

Email: kun.attila.hun@gmail.com

Mobile: 07884780121

SUMMARY

I am a developer with 10 years of experience. I started as a fullstack developer, then spent a couple of years working on performance-sensitive frontend applications. Recently I made a switch to C++ backend development on IG Group's trading platform. I like learning mathematics, physics and I'm also interested in machine learning. This made me complete a master's degree in Applied Statistics recently. I also like working on side projects, the latest of which can be visited at: https://attilakun.net/bloch

EDUCATION

Budapest University of Technology and Economics

Bachelor of Science (BSc), Software Engineering (2007-2011)

Birkbeck, University of London

Master of Science (MSc), Applied Statistics (2017-2019)

I finished the master's program with Distinction and I was awarded the second place of the Winton Prize for my final project in which I applied deep learning to an unsupervised learning problem. The report is available at: https://attilakun.net/project_report.pdf

EXPERIENCE

Automotive Process Institute GmbH Junior fullstack developer

2011-2014

- Client side development of a customer facing single page web application.
- Defined and implemented the JavaScript communication interface between the web and its native iOS host application.
- Contributed to the middleware layer using ASP.NET.
- Written and maintained stored procedures in Microsoft SQL Server.

IG Group Senior frontend developer 2014-2019

- Contributed to IG's real-time charting package written in JavaScript. The main library used was d3
- Participated in development of new features and many performance optimisation challenges on the frontend.
- Evaluated different solutions to plot financial data. This included experimentation with SVG, Canvas and WebGL.
- Led the adoption of TypeScript within the team.
- Contributed to the chart's integration test suite.
- A limited version of the chart is available at: https://www.ig.com/uk/indices/markets-indices/ftse-100

IG Group Backend developer 2019-present

- Contributed to IG's core pricing system. This involved development and maintenance of mainly C++ applications.
- Revised the scheduling and timezone management system.
- Worked on migrating backend services from FioranoMQ to ActiveMQ.

SKILLS